Finding Aid for Howard Cyrus Lawrence Papers 1916-1966
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Notebooks
  - Appointment books, address books, notebooks with political information, 1916-1960 (Box 25)
Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-
(Vice President of the United States)
Nov. 11, 1960
Norris, Louis William, 1906-
(MacMurray College)
1959-1961
North, Walter Harper, 1871-1952.
(Michigan Supreme Court)
Mar. 18, 1937, Apr. 19, 1937, Apr. 23, 1937
Nowicki, Leo J., 1904-
(Lieutenant Governor of Michigan)
Oct. 10, 1936
Osborn, Chase S. (Chase Salmon), 1860-1949.
(Governor of Michigan)
July 7, 1934, July 11, 1934, Sept. 1934-Jan. 1935, Mar. 1935-May 1935, Aug. 1935, Oct. 1935-Dec. 1935, Feb. 1936-Aug. 1936, Dec. 7, 1936, Dec. 16, 1936, Aug. 8, 19303, Aug. 12, 1938, Aug. 17, 1938, May 1939, Aug.-Nov. 1939, Jan. 12, 1940
Ott, Harvey N.
(Albion College trustee)
1930's-1961
Owen, R. Dwight.
(Grand Rapids, Michigan businessman)
1930's-1960
Pahl, Marvin F.
(Albion College)
1936-1961
Pollock, James Kerr, 1898-
(University of Michigan)
Mar. 31, 1952, Apr. 2, 1952, May 6, 1952
Potter, Charles E. (Charles Edward), 1916-
(United States Senator)
1952-1958
Potter, William W., 1869-1940.
(Michigan Supreme Court)
Mar. 29, 1934, May 21, 1934, May 22, 1934, Oct. 1, 1934, Oct. 4, 1934, June 6, 1936, June 22, 1936, July 2, 1936, Aug. 13, 1936, Aug. 27, 1936, Oct. 29, 1936, Oct. 30, 1936, Nov. 5, 1936, Nov. 17, 1936, May 24, 1939
Pryor, Millard H., 1901-
(Albion College trustee)
1940's-1961
Putnam, Mark Edson, 1886-
(Dow Chemical Company Midland, Michigan)
1930's-1960
Reed, Marshall Russell, 1891-
(Albion College trustee)
1930's-1961
Reichert, Rudolph Edward, 1887-1965.
(Michigan State Banking Commissioner)
Sept. 1935, Oct. 30, 1935, Nov. 19, 1935, Dec. 2, 1935, Jan. 11, 1936, Jan. 13, 1936, Mar. 3, 1936, Mar. 4, 1936, Mar. 18, 1936, Mar. 21, 1936, Apr. 11, 1936, Aug. 20, 1936
Nov. 17, 1936, Nov. 27, 1936, Dec. 31, 1936, Feb.-Mar. 1937, July 20, 1939 and occasionally to 1961
Ruthven, Alexander Grant, 1882-
(University of Michigan)
Oct. 17, 1941, Oct. 22, 1941, Nov. 12, 1941, Jan. 26, 1943, Jan. 30, 1943, Mar. 23, 1943
Seaton, John Lawrence, 1873-
(Albion College)
1935-1961
Sebastian, James R.
(Albion College trustee)
1930's-1961
Shackleton, James M., 1896-
(Saginaw State Bank)
1930's
Sharp, Alexander Jefferson.
(Albion College)
1950's
Sharpe, Nelson, 1858-1935.
(Michigan Supreme Court)
July 11, 1934, Oct. 21, 1935
Sigler, Kim, 1894-1953.
(Governor of Michigan)
May 15, 1941, May 16, 1941, May 17, 1941
Sink, Charles Albert, 1879-
(University of Michigan)
Nov. 12, 1924, Nov. 24, 1924, Mar. 3, 1934, Nov. 23, 1936, Dec. 31, 1936, June 24, 1941
Sligh, Charles Robert, 1906-
(Grand Rapids, Michigan businessman)
1950-1961
Slocum, William W., 1891-
(Albion College trustee)
1940's-1961
Smith, Delos Grosvenor, 1893-.
1940
Stassen, Harold Edward, 1907-
(Governor of Minnesota)
1940
Stough, Irvin K.
(American Home Security Bank, Grand Rapids, Michigan)
1936
Stowe, Ernest A., 1859-
1936
Summerfield, Arthur Ellsworth, 1899-
(Postmaster General of the United States)
May 19, 1945
Taylor, Malcolm Cameron, 1900-
(Ann Arbor Savings and Commercial Bank)
1930's and 1940's
Thompson, George.
(Michigan Trust Company, Grand Rapids, Michigan)
1930's-1945
Thompson, Harold R.
(Albion College trustee)
1940's-1961
Thomson, James Francis, 1892-
(Michigan Republican State Central Committee)
1937-1940
Toncray, Richard.
(Albion College trustee)
1930's-1961
Toy, Harry Stanley, 1892-
(Michigan Supreme Court)
Apr. 5, 1934, Apr. 20, 1934, Apr. 21, 1934, July 13, 1935, July 15, 1935, July 16, 1935
July 22, 1935, Feb. 27, 1939
Trautman, Paul R.
(Albion College)
1945-1961
Vandenberg., Arthur H. (Arthur Hendrick), 1884-1951.
(United States Senator)
1933-1936, Jan. 5, 1938, 1939-1940, 1942-1945
Vander Werp, Don, 1885-
(Member, Michigan Legislature)
Mar. 29, 1934, Apr. 2, 1934
VanOstenberg, Neal.
(American Home Security Bank, Grand Rapids, Michigan)
1930's
Van Wagoner, Murray Delos, 1898-
(Governor of Michigan)
Apr. 6, 1936, Apr. 10, 1936, June 11, 1936, June 16, 1936, July 20, 1936, July 30, 1937
July 31, 1940, Oct. 7, 1940, Nov. 14, 1940, June 4, 1941
Voorhies, Paul Warren, 1875-1952.
(Michigan Commissioner of Public Utilities)
1933-1952
Wade, Raymond J., 1875-
(Detroit, Michigan)
1940's-1961
Waldo, Dwight Bryant, 1864-1939.
(Western State Teachers College, Kalamazoo)
Apr. 1, 1935, Apr. 3, 1935, Apr. 4, 1935, Apr. 5, 1935
Walker, Louis Carlisle, 1875-1963.
(Muskegon, Michigan businessman)
1930's and 1940's
Watts, Frank B.
(Watts and Whelan Company, Detroit)
1935, Feb. 5, 1936, Feb. 12, 1936, Sept. 17, 1937, Sept. 20, 1937, Mar. 16, 1940, Mar. 29, 1940, May 13, 1940, Aug. 2, 1940, Dec. 14, 1940
Weber, Al H. 1870-
(Newspaper publisher, Cheboygan, Michigan)
Apr. 15, 1935, Apr. 18, 1935
Westerman, Leland.
(Grand Rapids, Michigan)
1941-1960
Whitehouse, William Whitcomb, 1891-
(Albion College)
1945-1961
Wier, E. G.
(Grand Rapids Furniture Makers Guild)
1940's and 1950's
Williams, Allan W. (Allan Mackenzie), 1892-1979.
(County Engineer, Ionia County, Michigan)
1930's-1961
Williams, Gerhard Mennen, 1911-
(Governor of Michigan)
Jan. 26, 1953
Willkie, Wendell L. (Wendell Lewis), 1892-1944.
(Republican Presidential Nominee)
June 19, 1940, June 20, 1940, June 23, 1940, June 27, 1940, Aug. 10, 1940, Aug. 19, 1940, Oct. 5, 1940, Oct. 11, 1940, Oct. 18, 1940, Oct. 26, 1940, Nov. 9, 1940, Jan. 1, 1941, Jan. 7, 1941, Jan. 10, 1941
Woodruff, Roy Orchard, 1876-1953.
(Congressman from Michigan)
Nov. 13, 1935, Feb. 26, 1937
Wright, James F.
(Pastor, First Methodist Church, Grand Rapids, Michigan)
1956-1961
Ziegler, Charles M., 1888-1959.
(Michigan State Highway Commissioner)
Mar. 18, 1937, Mar. 30, 1937